# Kaya Morris

Driven guest service agent with 1+ years of experience ensuring outstanding guest experiences in a high-end hotel with over 100 rooms. Polite and friendly interpersonal style and extensive knowledge of best practices in hotel customer service. Excellent computer skills and ability to generate effective solutions to operational and productivity challenges.

432 My Address Road, Phoenix, AZ 09876 k, m o rri\$@myema il.com (123)456-7890

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## **Guest Service Agent**

La Quinta by Wyndham, Phoenix, AZ June2019- Present

- Welcome guests warmly and conduct check-ins and check-outs using the point-of-sale system
- Maintain high standards of personal grooming and appearance in line with the Wyndham company policies
- Handle guest queries promptly and courteously and assist with restaurant and transport reservations
- Remain up-to-date with current offers, promotions, and services and communicate information clearly to guests
- Keep the front desk environment clean, attractive, and uncluttered and perform routine sanitization tasks

# Call Center Customer Service Representative

Cox Enterprises, Phoenix, AZ
January 2017 - Present

- Performed assessments to gain insights into customers' needs and match them with the most appropriate products and services
- Resolved queries and complaints via telephone and email and facilitated product returns
- Met and exceeded challenging sales targets under intense time pressure

### **EDUCATION**

Associate of Applied Sciences in Hospitality and Hotel Management

SCOTTSDALE COMMUNITY COLLEGE Scottsd a I e, AZ, Septem ber 2017-June 2019

### **KEY SKILLS**

- Cheerful and courteous customer service style
- Outstanding problem-solving ability
- learn player
- Extensive knowledge of local attractions and amenities
- Efficient and organized
- Excellent attention to detail
- Fluent in Spanish and French

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

FirstAidandCPR, 2020